Guide to the photograph album 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection AD.MC.030_ref165
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection, 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165; Lincoln, Edith; Lincoln, William P. (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_MC_030_ref165)
  - Top: Bas-reliefs of Cleopatra and Caesarion on a section of the back wall of the Temple of Hathor in the Temple of Dendera complex. Middle: The Temple of Dendera. Bottom: A bridge construction site., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000037_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Uniforms; Workers; Fez/Tarboush; Hats; Individual Portraits; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Dendera, Egypt; Construction; Bridges; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Water; Mountains/Hills
  - Top: A clipping entitled 'Upper-Egypt Luxor,' with a view of the Luxor Temple. Bottom Left: Cairo: Bazaar in the Mousky (a postcard showing men in the El Mosky Bazar, Cairo). Bottom Right: Luxor: Statues of Rameses II (a postcard of two statues of Rameses II in the Temple of Luxor)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000038_000001; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Statues/Sculptures; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Luxor, Egypt; Furnishings; Architecture; Buildings; Men; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Cairo, Egypt; Markets; Shops; Workers; Lanterns/Lamps; Streets/Roads; Facial Hair; Signs/Signposts; Printed Materials
  - Two views of the Luxor Temple., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000039_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Luxor, Egypt; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture
  - Two views of the statues of Ramesses II, and a woman sitting between two columns in the Luxor Temple., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000040_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Temples; Women; Hats; Individual Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Statues/Sculptures; Luxor, Egypt; Postcards; Egyptian Hieroglyphics
  - Two postcards of the pillars of Amenhotep III in the Luxor Temple. Top: Luxor Papyrus Pillar of Amenhotep III. Bottom: (No. 1501) Luxor Temple Papyrus Pillars of Amen Hotep III., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000041_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Temples; Postcards; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Men; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Luxor, Egypt
  - Two postcards of the pillars of Amenhotep III in the Luxor Temple. Top: Luxor Papyrus Columns of Amenhotep III. Bottom: (No. 1508) Luxor Temple Papyrus Columns of Amen Hotep III., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000042_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Architecture; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Palm Trees; Men; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Hats; Individual Portraits; Luxor, Egypt
  - A postcard of Luxor Temple - the colonnade., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000043_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Men; Individual Portraits; Temples; Mosques; Religious Sites; Luxor, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings; Regional/National Dress
  - Top: A woman next to the statues in the Luxor Temple. Bottom: Two postcards. Left: (No.1505) Luxor Temple: Wife of Rameses II (a statue of the wife of Ramesses II in the Luxor Temple). Right: (No.1506) Luxor Temple: Statue of Rameses II (a statue of Ramesses II)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000044_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Statues/Sculptures; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Women; Hats; Individual Portraits; Deserts; Mountains/Hills; Men; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Luxor, Egypt; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Unknown
  - Two postcards. Top: Luxor Temple: The Forecourt and Statues of Rameses II. Bottom: (No.1503) Luxor Temple: Pylon and Obelisk (a postcard of the pylon and obelisk in the Luxor Temple)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000045_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Architecture; Temples; Buildings; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Luxor, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Turbans; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Men; Egyptian Hieroglyphics
  - Two postcards. Top: Luxor. Pylon Statues and Obelisk of Rameses II (a postcard of statues and obelisk of Ramesses II). Bottom: (No.1504) Luxor - Mosque of Sheikh Abu el Haggag (a postcard of the Abou al-Haggag Mosque)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000046_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Temples; Donkeys; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Streets/Roads; Transportation; Animals; Men; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Buildings; Architecture; Individual Portraits; Mosques; Religious Sites; Luxor, Egypt
  - Top: a postcard of Nile steamers, with the Winter Palace Hotel in the background. Bottom: Two views of different reliefs both representing Min, the god of fertility., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000047_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Nile River; Rivers; Men; Children; Boys; Turbans; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Coast; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Hotels; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Luxor, Egypt; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues/Sculptures
  - Top: (No. 1510) A postcard of a sailboat crossing the Nile. Bottom Left: a relief. Bottom Right: columns in the Luxor Temple., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000048_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Boats/Ships; Men; Group Portraits; Water; Coast; Transportation; Nile River; Rivers; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Architecture; Buildings; Luxor, Egypt
  - Top: A postcard of a camel at the Temple of Queen Hatshepsut. Bottom: A view of the Temple of Hatshepsut., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000049_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Camels; Animals; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Mountains/Hills; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Architecture; Luxor, Egypt; Landscapes
  - Two views of the Temple of Hatshepsut., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000050_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Luxor, Egypt; Streets/Roads; Mountains/Hills; Crowds; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Landscapes
  - Top: A clipping entitled 'Upper-Egypt Thebes.' Bottom Left: The great Hypostyle Hall in Karnak. Bottom Right: Men in front of the Colossi of Memnon., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000051_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Men; Individual Portraits; Boys; Children; Streets/Roads; Group Portraits; Thebes, Egypt; Postcards; Printed Materials
  - A postcard of two men on the road to the Colossi of Memnon., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000052_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Streets/Roads; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Men; Children; Group Portraits; Thebes, Egypt; Postcards
  - A postcard of part of the Ramesseum and the largest statue of Ramesses II., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000053_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Individual Portraits; Luxor, Egypt
  - Three postcards. Top: (No. 1525) A view of the Ramesseum. Bottom Left: (No. 1526) A statue of Rameses in the Ramesseum. Bottom Right: (No. 1527) Reliefs in the Ramesseum., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000054_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Postcards; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Statues/Sculptures; Mountains/Hills; Deserts; Men; Individual Portraits; Turbans; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Edfu, Egypt
  - A man standing by a hillside with half-exposed structures., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000055_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Turbans; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Mountains/Hills; Architecture; Buildings; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Egypt; Tents
  - Three postcards. Top: (No. 1534) The statue of the goddess Sechet in Medinet Habu. Middle: (No. 1533) The Temple of Rameses III in Medinet Habu. Bottom: (No. 1535) The pavillion of the Temple of Rameses III., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000056_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Turbans; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Temples; Group Portraits; Egypt
  - A blank page in the 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000057_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
  - Top: A clipping entitled 'Upper-Egypt Karnak.' Bottom: A postcard of the Gateway of Ptolomey (entrance to the Temple of Khonsu)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000058_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Printed Materials; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Palm Trees; Architecture; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Temples; Luxor, Egypt; Donkeys; Men; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Buildings
  - A blank page in the 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000059_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
  - Top: A view of the Amun Temple. Bottom: Two views of the Statue of Amun Ra at Karnak Temple, Luxor, Egypt., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000060_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Statues/Sculptures; Buildings; Men; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Women; Hats; Group Portraits; Luxor, Egypt
  - Two postcards. Top: A view of the Temple of Amun Ra with the sacred lake. Bottom: A view of the Temple of Amun Ra., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000061_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Lakes; Water; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Landscapes; Luxor, Egypt; Streets/Roads
  - Two postcards showing views of the Temple of Amun Ra., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000062_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Temples; Men; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Streets/Roads; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Luxor, Egypt
  - Two postcards showing views of the Temple of Rameses III., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000063_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Temples; Luxor, Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues/Sculptures; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Women; Hats; Group Portraits; Bags/Purses; Head Covers/Veils
  - Top: Reliefs on a temple's facade. Bottom: A woman standing in a temple., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000064_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Women; Hats; Individual Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Temples; Egypt
  - Three postcards. Top: A man standing next to the Temple of Opet. Bottom: (No. 1518 and 1519) Two views of the Hypostyle Hall in Karnak., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000065_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Men; Regional/National Dress; Camels; Animals; Turbans; Hats; Individual Portraits; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Buildings; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Luxor, Egypt
  - Top: A postcard depicting the memorials of Thutmose III in Karnak. Bottom: An Egyptian relief depicting animals and plants from the botanical garden wall at the Temple of Karnak, February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000066_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Statues/Sculptures; Palm Trees; Streets/Roads; Men; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Luxor, Egypt; Animals
  - Two postcard views of the Avenue of the Sphinxes in Karnak., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000067_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues/Sculptures; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Palm Trees; Landscapes; Men; Donkeys; Regional/National Dress; Animals; Mountains/Hills; Boys; Children; Individual Portraits; Luxor, Egypt
  - Three views of the Avenue of the Sphinxes in Karnak., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000068_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Streets/Roads; Architecture; Buildings; Landscapes; Palm Trees; Mountains/Hills; Luxor, Egypt; Horses; Animals; Statues/Sculptures; Men; Individual Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Regional/National Dress
  - Three portraits of people in their village., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000069_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Children; Men; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Tents
  - Top and Middle: Two views of sailboats with passengers. Bottom: A group of men wearing fezes in the desert., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000070_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Water; Mountains/Hills; Egypt; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Boys; Children; Turbans; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Deserts
  - General views of the Valley of the Kings., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000071_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Streets/Roads; Tents; Buildings; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Mountains/Hills; Architecture; Men; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Luxor, Egypt; Tombs/Mausoleums
  - Top: A view of Tutankhamen's Tomb. Bottom: A view of the Valley of the Kings., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000072_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Buildings; Men; Uniforms; Fez/Tarboush; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Tombs/Mausoleums; Streets/Roads; Mountains/Hills; Luxor, Egypt; Group Portraits
  - A view of the first coffin of King Tutankhamen., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000073_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Coffins/Caskets; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Tombs/Mausoleums; Luxor, Egypt; English Writing
  - Mural paintings in Tomb 9 of Rameses V and VI., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000074_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tombs/Mausoleums; Paintings; English Writing; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Luxor, Egypt
  - Mural paintings in the side chamber of the Tomb of Seti I in the Valley of the Kings., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000075_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Paintings; Tombs/Mausoleums; Luxor, Egypt; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Boats/Ships; Transportation
  - A mural painting from the Tomb of Rameses I., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000076_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Paintings; Tombs/Mausoleums; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Animals; Luxor, Egypt
  - A view of bridge construction., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000077_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Bridges; Streets/Roads; Water; Crowds; Landscapes; Egypt
  - Group portraits of two crowds., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000078_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Hats; Men; Children; Boys; Crowds; Fez/Tarboush; Palm Trees; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps; Girls
  - Top: A clipping entitled, 'Upper-Egypt Edfou-Komombo.' Bottom: Two postcard views of reliefs in the Temple of Horus, Edfou., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000079_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Printed Materials; Edfu, Egypt; Men; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Egyptian Hieroglyphics
  - Three postcards. Top: (No. 1572) Pillar-vestibule in the Temple of Horus. Bottom: (No. 1568 and 1571) Two views of the Temple of Horus., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000080_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Statues/Sculptures; Men; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Architecture; Buildings; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Egyptian Hieroglyphics
  - Views of the Temple of Horus., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000081_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Edfu, Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Fez/Tarboush; Hats
  - Three postcards. Top: (No. 1572) Pillar-vestibule in the Temple of Horus. Bottom: (No. 1568 and 1571) Two views of the Temple of Horus., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000082_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Temples; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Architecture; Buildings; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Edfu, Egypt
  - A newspaper clipping showing a portion of the outer wall at the Temple of Komombo., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000083_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Printed Materials; Architecture; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Edfu, Egypt; Temples; Statues/Sculptures
  - Top: (No. 1573) The Temple of Horus. Bottom: A woman sitting at the Temple of Horus., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000084_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Women; Hats; Individual Portraits; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Deserts; Edfu, Egypt
  - Top: (No. 1575) A postcard view of the Temple of Kom Ombo. Bottom: A general view of the Temple of Kom Ombo., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000085_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Water; Boats/Ships; Temples; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Transportation; Buildings; Aswan, Egypt
  - A newspaper clipping showing a relief in the Temple of Kom Ombo: "The gods Thoth and Horus pouring the water of life over the king.", February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000086_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Printed Materials; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Statues/Sculptures; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Aswan, Egypt
  - Top: A view of the Temple of Kom Ombo from far away. Bottom Left: A relief depicting Ptolemy between two divinites of Upper Egypt, Temple of Kom Ombo. Bottom Right: (No. 1577) A relief in the Temple of Kom Ombo depicting Horus writing the life of Philometer., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000087_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Temples; Landscapes; Water; Aswan, Egypt; Postcards; Men; Boys; Children; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Architecture; Buildings; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues/Sculptures; Rivers; Nile River
  - Top: (No. 1576) The Temple of Kom Ombo seen from the Nile. Bottom: (No. 1574) An overhead view of the Temple of Kom Ombo., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000088_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Nile River; Rivers; Men; Children; Group Portraits; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Aswan, Egypt; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Statues/Sculptures; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Water
  - Top: A cutout depicting the Nile steamers 'Delta' and 'Thebes.' Bottom: A cartoon advertisment for Cook's Nile Services., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000089_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Mountains/Hills; Nile River; Rivers; Water; Flags; Printed Materials; Men; Women; Children; Donkeys; Animals
  - The passenger list for Cook's Nile Services steamer 's.s. Thebes.', February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000089_000002; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Printed Materials; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Travel; Nile River; Rivers
  - From the top left clockwise: A man holding a donkey, the Temple of Kom Ombo from afar, a man leaning on columns while holding a sword, and a postcard (No. 1579) showing a relief of the crowning of Philomete in the Temple of Kom Ombo., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000090_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)